The perfect opportunity is right in front of you, just to
welcome you. Hello Sanjeev ji, good day.
Tell me where are you tracking the momentum?
You are here today. So,
see, the entry numbers are very
good, so the short term money has moved into that,
but I am still thinking bank
category and in that, I will tell you that 37,000, whatever you call Bank
Nifty, it is going to come, whether it came in 15 days or
a month, but there is a front in the bank and there is a lot
in the midcap bank today. The
commentary that has come today is Bandhan Bank and Ramesh Majha
Microfinance, they say that the landing is
dam recovery 25%, September tweet
98% 100, I request the people of Bandhan etc. to get
famous in Bandhan, RBL Bank, IDFC, you will be rich report, let me give you the
update of midcap bank Rubaru circle. I had
given you entry finance of 9350 earlier,
95.50 went, book profit in that and
making ₹2 handsome. You have two pics here. Let me
also tell you that the tube bank of 1035, I
gave a task of 1150  It has become 1185
so probably micro finance law and urban
bank class on destiny will be today's two picks if
you say so I will start phone ji machine
safe badh
lips first will be ICICI Lombard
insurance from the ground and insurance Guddu
Yadav stream ICICI Lombard and
testing 1658 character 215 take in 34540
stoploss is 1510 12 going back to
more than 60 Bahubali my favorite
updates UP Bank of Baroda Bank of
Baroda will give the highest record profit in this quarter
which is your July end
attributes take in 884 that bus stop love
7250 decided to ₹90 ok so
ambulance packing machine sa pa on long reference from Bank of Baroda
today's hot topic of
discussion na market is hot that time totka of
your what is the reward should you invest money should you invest
in the final of 7276 rupees
see every caution whatever the trend is it is
telling this so  Trends and friend events
everywhere are spreading its price up. It's fiction,
but this talk will make money over the
next few years. To figure out where it's headed
and used to give you. You're written
with this business news. No brainer. However, as
I told you, there's no metric for its valuation
before, so it's
difficult to comment. But I think you must have this in
your portfolio in small
quantities. This is a very well-grounded opinion.
Machine snakes seem to be staying put for now.
And on midcap IT, is there any specific reason why you should
subscribe to midcap IT that you had found so much. So,
this ruling should be done.
Score for reminder. We have
gone from a very low level. Still, I think in reality, should we go
into a serial Tech Mahindra deal? Will it give you something? But
today I'm by
students. Lapet Yadav. Banking stocks.
If I see Bank of Baroda at 140, I will
focus on that or RBL. I
see Jhade 400 or 350 and so
I see a lot of monk in midcap banks
and this is it.  Core but I like it, I admitted it has been a very very
big
outperformer however most validation
drinks ringgit the real ball will commit
midcap bank listen so I camp banks
Bandhan Bank of Baroda and machine sir on bell I have been
seeing you giving a pistol call and technical call for a long time now it has been 50 minutes
their interest